I felt like um I felt like Shannon was
playing in my face and he eventually
turned the corner but and then but then
at the end of the interview like he
just like I don't know just kind of like
chilling me and Shannon were
flirting ma'am if you don't get all the
way out of here with that [ __ ]
please don't insult me um and
that was
offensive that was highly offensive and
it makes me wonder if you know when
people are flirting with you
um so when I left the interview I just
was very like kind of not sure how it
was going to play out and I knew that he
had played himself in the interview in a
number of time in a number of ways and
so I knew that he would
um they would probably edit some of it
out so that's how I felt
um have you seen his prior
interviews he's very welcoming and
bubbly
he the door is open folks talk
uninterrupted he allows them to be a
safe space the producer told me I would
be in a safe space and told me you know
I'd be I would be
supported so that's what I
expected he didn't behave with me
like he he has not behaved with anybody
else like he did with me so that's why I
did the
interview um okay any other
questions you know what I don't feel
like it showed
my so it's weird when you when we talk
about like truth right like so yes like
I got to speak honestly about certain
things but I don't feel like it showed
my truth because it showed me in defense
mode and I don't exist in defense mode
so um it it it it put me on my heels a
little bit where I felt like I had
to um you know just kind of do a lot
more
explaining and it was a bit exhausting
like mentally
so uh you know just like the like I had
to really like kind of manage the
interview and that's really different
now it's beautiful like when you get to
do interviews where you really get to
just be like you feel like you're like
being you're liberated in the
conversation and to be honest when I did
the Jason Lee interview like that's how
I felt like the Jason Lee interview just
felt
really I mean like he's going to throw
some messiness at you but he didn't
press you on it and it just didn't feel
like I was having to you know really use
like all of my syntax like all of my
synapse to like navigate but nonetheless
um I
um and I feel like something I learned
from watching it was that I have a
tendency
to um like my mom is up is very
pessimistic like she'll always go the
negative route and I saw it play out on
the episode because there were times
where he would ask me a question and I
would be about to give like a positive
answer but then he would throw a
negative spin on it and then I would
just follow that lead and that is
something I need to be more mindful of
uh just in the future in general because
I shouldn't be letting somebody like
lead me down that road
um and so I need to be more uh just
mindful of
that
um no there will not be a part
two so many of y'all have been on my
head like don't you ever go on that
platform again so I
will I will
not oh thank you entertainment takeover
I appreciate
you
[Music]
um I did have regret because I felt
like I felt like I had made a big
mistake
in like sharing so much and and just
being so um
kind of
just my full unmask like onest s
and then that turned by the end of the
day
because I'm not I'm trying not to look
at comments but I was looking at the DMS
and so many of you all felt so
seen in the interview and you felt like
you had somebody that was speaking your
truth and so that made it all the worth
wow like completely made it all the
worthwhile and um yeah so no I don't I
don't regret it anymore in the beginning
of the day like I literally had to step
away from the radio show and cry and
come back because I just
felt like I was so hyperfocused I I
literally didn't eat today like I just
realized this I have to go eat so I'm
doing this quickly because I realized I
have to go eat I did not eat today I had
like some almonds and some pretzels with
almond butter so I've ODed on the Almond
um
yeah the pivot definitely would have
been a dope
option
um did you feel listened to fairly no
um but I also don't want to be S here I
don't want to sit here and like I don't
you know I don't need siop Fant either
but
um yes there were some things cut out uh
it was cut out when they cut out when he
said to me it seems like you think that
anytime someone doesn't agree with you
that they're racist and I said well I
mean it's too early in this conversation
to say that and he said
um no I said like what what in this
conversation would make you feel that
way and he said uh well I feel that way
because you just talked about autism
being racism and you just talked about
your teacher being racist
and so then I explained the um you know
the racism attached to autism diagnosis
and why it's like so difficult for
people to get clinical
diagnosis uh from like you know because
it's like $10,000 and also because as a
black woman you're often times um
misdiagnosed and then uh they cut out
where I said to him like didn't you
leave your last job because
of
racism and he was
like um
and they also cut out when I spoke about
Palestine even though briefly uh they
cut out when I spoke about
Palestine
and uh they cut out at the end he was
asking no I have not been clinically
diagnosed by a doctor because I'm not
paying $10,000
to do that and most people will tell you
that at this age you don't need a
clinical diagnosis in the in that sense
and I think that's the other thing it's
like we are so um conditioned here in
this nation
to um really only consider something in
one kind of way and uh I will get back
to that the other thing that they cut
out is um
he was saying that
um he was
saying
that what's it
called hold on he was saying that
um I guess Caitlyn Jenner said uh
basically
that she said like good riddance I guess
when OJ died and he was asking me about
that and I said said and he was like I
how do you feel about that and I was
like I mean you know I don't really know
but
[Music]
um he was like I just don't think we
should celebrate when people die and I
was like
well I mean when the queen died I
definitely was like good riddens and he
was like oh I'm just not that kind of
person I just I I just not that kind of
person I wouldn't do that and I was
like so you telling me that if you went
back in time and you had the capability
to to see your former enslave your your
people's former your people's enslaver
uh put put in the ground you wouldn't do
a little fist pump he was like nah N I
wouldn't do it I would n I'm just I
wasn't raised that way I wasn't raised
that way I said [ __ ] I
was
so that was that
um um
no I won't be here when I get back so I
am really ADR like I really was like I'm
G to talk about this today and I will
not talk about it again I will not talk
about it again I will not so that's why
I was like let me hop on this thing and
do a little B talking
um and give people you know more space
and energy around it because I'm not
going to do it anymore
oh that's what's up keyock I'm really
glad that
happened
[Music]
um if there's any so you know if you
have any more questions so for some
reason you
can't you can't when badges are on you
can't put questions on the screen so all
of y'all who left questions in the
little question bubble just put it on
the
screen
um sing a black man
listen this was wild this was wild to me
cuz I I was I was like I
can't I can't make that make
sense I can't I can't make it make
sense um I just I I was really
flabbergasted by it
so
um you know I know right I really want
to do this sh with Jeff Foxworthy like
just us in a boat fishing talking about
you know just America and our different
experiences like I really like Jeff
Foxworthy was really super kind like and
we did have conversations like it was
just it was really
dope um yeah I do do I think people feel
intimidated by you
yeah and it's unfortunate cuz it's like
uncomfortable and it just makes it feel
like you got to do [ __ ] to make people
feel comfortable and then sometimes you
do [ __ ] to make people feel comfortable
and then they feel some type of way that
you doing [ __ ] to make people feel
comfortable so it's like you can't win
and
um I just
don't I just don't think
that I should be labored with that
um what remember you had me try a lamb
Samosa in Sonoma California I don't
remember that of course they're
intimidated
because y'all are
funny um
I I did right I really was
[Music]
like
um I don't feel trapped in the system
anymore and I feel like this interview
really helped me to like like Propel
myself out of that system too you know I
meant it when I said like I burnt
Bridges today and I did that on purpose
and I burnt Bridges yesterday too like
well that actually they had already
burnt the bridges I just you know
sparked the last Timbers of it all
cuz I'm just not having it no
more I've been on anti-depressants
for I think two months now and um my
experience has been really great I feel
like it's just been been it's just
allowed me to handle
things um better and I it doesn't affect
me in a way that I don't feel like I'm
on medication but it I definitely feel
like I'm more regulated and I was having
a really hard time doing
that yeah I would absolutely do Sherry
Jennifer Hudson or Tamarind I've done
Tamarind before I supp Tam the other day
um I've never met Jennifer but Sherry is
the homie too but you know I want I just
need to take a break from just being in
the mix like that and I'm going be on
this tour so get your
tickets
um that's you know that's really
it my goal in the entertainment industry
moving forward is to not be a part of
the entertainment industry I want to
just be
liberated completely I want to exist as
Amanda seals like I don't want to have
um you know like I don't even want to
have this title of comedian or actress
or Etc like I just really want to exist
as Amanda seals and like folks are just
kind of going along with um or taking in
you know just the different creative as
Adventures that I'm putting out there as
they see fit and that's what I really
want to do I don't want to exist within
any of these boxes that I had to put
myself in in order to make it make sense
hey Robert and um and you know and like
Robertson here we went to purchase
together like he known me 20
[ __ ] years like I've always
been that person like just a multi hyen
it and I really feel like I got to I I
want to go there and yes I really want
to sell my art
full-time thank you so much and that is
something I am definitely driving
towards and uh
papay said I feel this interview
Vindicated you tonight I've been telling
my wife you're the truth forever and won
her over with your honesty
thanks usually it's the opposite usually
it's the wife trying to win the the
husband over trying to tell them to get
on the Manda seals train but uh I
appreciate that so much and tell your
wife I said thank
you well well I it's not that I get
scared or doubt my opinions I mean I
think it's just that I'm always I'm
always ready
to to admit when I'm wrong even though
people love to say I don't take
accountability that's just [ __ ] not
true like I will say hey like I used to
think such and such and now I know XYZ
and so now I think such and such and the
thing about it is that people want you
to do these big grandiose Declarations
of apology to them as individuals cuz
sometime somehow that feels that makes
them feel like they need it and it's not
it's not about you as an indiv idual
so um you know my opinions are grounded
in research they're grounded in
information like I'm not just speaking
about [ __ ] off my out my
neck so I I don't really have a fear
about my indep my opinions because I
don't speak them um you know I don't
speak them
gratuitously all right I'mma take two
more questions hey Gary
um will you share your ways of living up
your art I'm just starting out and I
don't want to be in putting any more
boxes either you know I got to be honest
with you you know I think I had to go in
the boxes when I started out you know
because it's like I had
to make a way for myself because I
needed
to pay um
for my bills and I don't work well under
um Financial Jess like some folks do
some folks you know like that that
starving artist Trope like some people
really do feel like they worked their
best when they got like their back
against the wall and I don't feel that
way
so I feel like there was um something to
be said around just like having to go in
the Box to get to get financial like
stability I think there's also something
in just the process like I went in these
different boxes um and and really like
marinated in them you know and learned
and so when you're a true multi hyen it
you really do have to like take up space
in certain spaces to get your your
processes down and to EV to ex to
expound and to evolve so it's like you
know I've been a DJ in a real way I've
been a um MC in a real way I've been a
comedian in a real way um so you know
I've been actor in a real way so like
all of these things have I've committed
to them in real ways even though I
didn't stop doing the other things and
so when they all came together now I'm
at a point of Mastery where I'm just
like I
really I can make my own box and it took
time and it took time so I don't want to
I don't want to tell you that that's
your journey but that's what my journey
was um and I think that there's
something that I hope there's something
that you can take from
there um the black media you would ask
like what do I think black media should
do I mean I just think you know black
media is a weird ass word at this point
like even like your page is called the
black media but you you possibly are the
only black media I see actually
representing what I thought black media
was supposed to do in this digital space
which is you know protect black folks I
feel like you have you know thoughtful
commentary and even though we don't
agree on things all the time it it it's
irrelevant
because your heart is in the same place
all the time and that is wholly clear
and um you know abundant like at the end
of the day like you should I hate when
people tell me like you know I don't
agree with you all the time because it's
like well you don't agree with anyone
all the time but do you feel but do you
feel like their core and their and their
character is consistent CU that's the
thing that you got to look
at um you know that's what that's what
you got to look at does that consistency
so show up
and I think
um you know I think you know be instead
of critical thinking a lot of these
folks out here is doing critical hating
you know they doing literally critical
hating they just trying to like look all
in the nooks and crannies to find how
they could hate and I just thought that
was that that is just so under it's so
stupid it's like such a n it's such an
irrel um what's what I'm looking for
it's such
an G I Can't think it's just so it's
dumb it's dumb um pen do you feel like
you have a hard time having positive
experiences with co-workers and people
overall
no I feel like I have a hard time just
being in the
world that's something I've had a hard
time with just being
alive living
and I think
[Music]
um you know
doing communicating with um no I'm not
going to have no conversation with
Isa
no
um I think it's it's
like I've been in spaces that I didn't
belong because I've been in spaces that
don't accommodate people like me and and
I'm not even talking about the autism I
just mean
like they just there spaces that are for
self it's so for self so like if you're
not on that like you're not going
to
um you're not going to fit you know
you're just not going to fit
so um that can be a [ __ ]
but I feel like there's just like
there's a very frighteningly incorrect
representation of me and this idea of
like Amanda having a hard time in like
work spaces it's like no Amanda will not
let you [ __ ] play in her
[ __ ] face she will not she will
not she will not she will not and I'm in
the business of people who literally
wake up every day who's face gonna play
today like that's like their whole emmo
you know what I'm saying so like nah I I
just I'm not going to do that and so yes
I have trouble with those people
true um
your disconnect between your self
perception and public perception I I
don't have a disconnect between my self
perception and public perception that I
just have an annoyance and and a
frustration with the fact that um you
know unfortunately public perception is
subjective and we live in a world and a
nation that often has this idea that
you're only supposed to show up one way
in order to be
correct so like for instance I am a very
Stern person I'm a very um intense
person so for some people that feels
like so that feels like um a strict
parent but then to other people just
feel like that's a teacher you know to
some people that feels like a drill
sergeant to some people that feels like
a coach that's just trying to get the
best out of you so it's really about
subjectivity and ultimately I cannot
affect like how people receive me but
there is a constant expectation that I
need to speak a certain way and that
that way that I need to speak is going
to be a better way for people to receive
me but at the end of the day if I being
authentic then that is not the goal like
to me I am I am a beacon of authenticity
and that is really what I'm here to be
and I don't have time to do all of that
dancing when there's so much other so
many other places to put my my energy so
no I don't have a disconnect from my
self perception and public perception
I'm watching I'm watching the interview
I'm like well yeah I see why people
watch this and say unlikable cuz I'm un
flinching I'm unflappable and that that
is very um and I'm intense and I'm on my
defense because someone is coming at me
and I'm having to cut through the
[ __ ] Haze and the [ __ ] that they
throwing at me so I really appreciate
the people who watch that and like could
see what was going because um they could
see that oh like this is somebody who is
you know being tested and is really
keeping their they're cool and they're
calm and you know um not being a and not
being moved people are saying I'm
whining because those are people that
don't feel like they have a voice and so
it is frustrating to see me have a voice
when they don't have it and so they'll
just try to write it off and then people
will say she you know why does she have
a voice like why she always talking why
she complaining you know she doesn't
have struggle blah BL BL BL BL that's
just not true I just
strugle
um listen if I exibited everything that
I'm exhibiting now as a man this would
not be a discussion if I exhibited
everything I did now as a man y'all
would be like this is not y have pictur
like your house facts that be be like on
my head that's that's why man if my head
we gotta get out of here we gotta get
out of here so um and because go Brown
this what she is she send me screenshots
of nice comments she's like I hope
comments um
so um will he air the episode what you
what you talking about um so I'm gonna
go eat and I have to you know just kind
of watch some cartoons I'm watch Xmen
and I just appreciate y'all if you
haven't got your ticket to see me on
tour.com um the unlikable tour is is out
here okay and all these shows should be
sold out every single one of them uh am
I done with acting for the time being
yeah
my e